questions = [
    {
        "question":"Who composed Music for a While?",
        "correctAnswer":"Henry Purcell",
        "answer0":"Johann Sebastian bach",
        "answer1":"Antonio Vivaldi",
        "answer2":"George Frederic Handel"
    },
    {
        "question":"What era is Music for a While from?",
        "correctAnswer":"Baroque",
        "answer0":"Classical",
        "answer1":"Medieval",
        "answer2":"Romantic"
    },
    {
        "question":"What key is Music for a While in?",
        "correctAnswer":"A Minor",
        "answer0":"A Major",
        "answer1":"G Minor",
        "answer2":"C Minor"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which instrument is not featured in Music for a While?",
        "correctAnswer":"Cello",
        "answer0":"Harpsichord",
        "answer1":"Bass Viol",
        "answer2":"Vocals"
    },
    {
        "question":"What does the left hand of the Harpsichord play?",
        "correctAnswer":"Ground Bass",
        "answer0":"Riff",
        "answer1":"Ostinato",
        "answer2":"Chords"
    },
    {
        "question":"What word describes when the music reflects the meaning of a word?",
        "correctAnswer":"Word Painting",
        "answer0":"Syllabic",
        "answer1":"Melismatic",
        "answer2":"Falsetto"
    },
    {
        "question":"What type of voice sings Music for a While?",
        "correctAnswer":"Soprano",
        "answer0":"Tenor",
        "answer1":"Alto",
        "answer2":"Bass"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the texture?",
        "correctAnswer":"Homophonic",
        "answer0":"Polyphonic",
        "answer1":"Heterophonic",
        "answer2":"Monophonic"
    },
    {
        "question":"What technique is used for the dissonance of 'pains'",
        "correctAnswer":"Word painting",
        "answer0":"Improvisation",
        "answer1":"Ornamentation",
        "answer2":"Melisma"
    },
    {
        "question":"What word describes decorations added to the melody?",
        "correctAnswer":"Ornamentation",
        "answer0":"Dissonance",
        "answer1":"Improvisation",
        "answer2":"Suspensions"
    },
    {
        "question":"How can the melody be described?",
        "correctAnswer":"Stepwise",
        "answer0":"Ascending",
        "answer1":"Descending",
        "answer2":"Disjunct"
    }
]